Hello hello friends welcome to my channel Aisa
2 and here we talk about many things
but in simple language which can be understood by everyone so
if you are troubled by Coronavirus right now
and you are afraid of
what will happen if you get Coronavirus and how much will it cost to treat it then
this is the place where you have come
here today we are going to discuss
about our body so let's start so
first let's understand the situation of corona virus right now if we
look at the numbers of the whole world then more than 93 lakh people have got it
in the whole world and this number is
increasing by 160 thousand every day if we
look at the condition of India then more than 450,000
people have to get it and
more than 15,000 people are being completely suppressed every day
and when we all start going out of the house then
this number can increase even faster
so on our channel you are staying at home as much as
you can
now let's see
how much it costs to treat corona virus now you will
not believe how much it costs
If you have to go for a blood test for any virus,
then the
cost of one test is 2400 and a patient needs
more than one. Apart from this, due to fiber deficiency, the
hospital cost for one day is
18,000. Apart from this, if you go to the hospital
or cannot do it at home, we have
companies like Reliance General
Insurance companies, in which you get
this front. First of all,
in Reliance, you have the option of 500 to one year, you
get one and a half of 50,000 or more.
In Star Health, you
get the opportunity of 31 thousand or 42000. Whereas in Indian and
Salman, you always have the option of one or two, one or two,
in third house, you have medical officers, that is,
if you take this much money, you
need 70075. Whereas in other cities, it is like
how to spend the entire money, then
subscribe to Reliance and Digit Home and you have tightened your body completely.
But keep in mind that in Star, you will have to go to the
hospital to get the full money.
Rest of the Indians and Uber app hospitals  There is
no need to go,
I have different formats for you, for example,
in Salumber, only
people between 18 and 75 years can take it, whereas
if you need a day for your children, then there is
Reliance which takes admission from children of three categories above, the
waiting period in all of them is 15
days, only in Indian time, not in Indian time,
meaning if you take admission today, you
cannot clear it for the next 15 days, there are
entry restrictions in all of them,
only in Indian time,
Reliance says that if you have been travelling from India in the last 45 days, do
not visit episode 382 number and this number is also mentioned
that you should not try after 31 December 19
or else if you go into details, then
in Reliance you will get free
hospitalization operation, which means if you are in
pipeline, then whatever expenses you have incurred in the last 30 days
or after being released from the hospital, you will
get the result of that, it also
gives you some benefits, ambulance
is your option if you are interested, family now next
week apart from you, Indian time also if  If you
take the patient to the hospital for urgent medical treatment
in a presidential or military city, you will be charged 50%.
In an isolation ward, you get online consultation with a doctor, and
ambulance facilities.
Hospitalization expenses are covered under BEST.
Like Reliance, you get
air and you also get ambulance cover,
including your favorites. But the problem with Digit is
that if you are not subscribed to Digit, you can
subscribe to it if you want. If you are subscribed to Digit, you can
subscribe. If you are subscribed to Digit, you can subscribe. If you are subscribed to Digit, you can
subscribe. If you like, you can subscribe.
Now the question arises, where can you buy it? If you
go to their website, you won't get it.
For this, you will have to go through an application.
For Reliance, you will have to go to Paytm
so that you can get this
remedy. Start In,
you will have to go to Indian Airtel, thanks.
But you will have to become a customer of Airtel Payments Bank. The
isolation ward will be sent to
you on Flipkart,
and the fuel will be available. Digit's
share will be available on Flipkart, this issue will be available on the phone.
Keep in mind, only Avatar.  Except this,
you will get everything else only in mobile applications,
not on the website. So,
what is the thing to keep in mind
after this video, one coronavirus is increasing, so
a natural one. Yes son, if you do
not believe in your vision, there are two types of insurance,
one which improves the expenses, the
other which can cover the entire money of the job in advance.
The best thing is that you do
not need any medical test, so for this, keep in mind the pre-
preparedness period and travel history
and the last minute test is always done by ICMR. I
love you all, the government has said the right thing, I will
put the list of medicines there, you
can check
which is the nearest centre to you. Thank you for watching this video.
If you like the video, then
share it with your friends and family.
Like the video. We are going to make many videos
now to explain things in more easy language,
so subscribe and
press the bell icon. Thank you.